Hi everyone! I'm here with...
Hi, Ruby Alexia and this is Backstage at German Fetish Bowl.
Thank you.
For Celine I'm planning a high ponytail and then we've got this beautiful little blue
little ponytail wig that I'm going to attach to her own hair.
It's gonna look gorgeous.
I think my makeup for today is just going to be normal smokey eye makeup.
So nothing too fancy but I fancy hair.
Yeah.
You're starting to procreate us for the show.
Eating some pizza, the last time I guess, today.
So, the preparation starts.
I just need a bottle.
Hi, I'm Nai.
I'm working tonight for Pandora Deluxe.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
It's in a sanctum and yeah it's less but I like it.
Thank you.
The photo was amazing!
Thank you so much!
It was amazing, it's been so long, it was so great to see everyone and we were having
such a good team. We waited so long for it. It was so fun thanks to all the
models and everyone. They made the show. So on a fair you wait for two and a half years and then it's over in one minute.
Cheers!
So we're done finally, the show is over and now we're gonna stop drinking
and we're chilling in the backstage area
and finally we meet each other
and we met now, finally
so we're gonna have an awesome night
and stay here at the party
Cheers!
Thank you.